Looks like a doll's house.
It is a bit like a doll's house.
This is loose,
so you can get underneath this.
-This is 5'9".
-JAGGER: Why?
So the back-line guys can get in
and out of there.
Look at those balconies.
It might be nice to get them
out there, from... One wide.
You know what I mean, Bob?
Hand-held.
RICHARDSON: Well, that we can do.
I don't know.
I have no idea why
the stage is designed in this way.
lf there's any really rhyme
or reason to it.
-Which part?
-All of it.
-You wanted it.
-I never asked for those.
That's Marty that wanted all of those.
I thought he wanted those.
So we got them now.
I hope he likes them.
(SINGING UNDER MY THUMB)
I don't know what's going on.
I did a hundred things overthere,
but nothing that I needed to do.